### **ALEKSANDR ANDREYKO**

#### Middle Frontend Developer

+374 (98) 990665 # www.linkedin.com/in/chgrin/ # marphalina@gmail.com # telegram: @chgrin

Commercial experience: over 4 years. For the last 3 years I was working as the only frontend developer in the team, which taught me to understand the areas of responsibility and set fair assessments of tasks.

Besides my main work, I am actively studying the typescript+react stack, and I am going to switch to it.

I am engaged in teaching several students, which helps me to keep my knowledge in good shape.

I am fond of cycling and it is a great way to recharge my batteries!

#### **SKILLS**

HTML	CSS	Jav	aScript	jQuery	Sass	Stylu	us Git	React	Redux
TypeScript	Webp	ack	Babel	npm	Docker	Jira	Agile	Bitrix	Laravel

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Frontend Developer I National Media Group, Moscow, Russia December 2020 - October 2023

Support and development of new functionality for the channel sites of CTC Media holding (**domashniy.ru**, **chetv.ru**, **ctclove.ru**) and some third-party projects, for example, the website of a film project pitching contest **pitchlab.ctcmedia.ru**.

Refactoring and getting rid of legacy on projects.

The stack is used on the following projects:

- js + react + redux/redux toolkit + a bit jquery + preprocessors (stylus/sass)
- webpack for assembly, or rather webpack-mix from laravel
- · laravel on backend

### Implemented tasks of different levels:

- user authorization
- adding a subscription to view content without ads
- complete redesign of the site
- participation in the migration of projects to another backend framework
- splitting site elements into independent widgets and optimizing their loading

# Jr Frontend Developer I Leomax, Moscow, Russia August 2019 - December 2020

Development of a landing page for the company's products on React. Support and creation of new sections in current online shops (jquery + yii) and (jquery + bitrix).

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Programming algorithms | Yandex Contest | 2023 - Present

Sorting algorithms

#### Frontend | Self-Education | 2020 - Present

React, Redux, Webpack, Typescript

#### Frontend Developer I GeekBrains, Online I 2020

HTML, CSS, React

#### Frontend Developer I HTMLAcademy, Online I 2019

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

#### **Advertising and Multimedia Technology Specialist**

#### The First Moscow Educational Complex | Moscow, Russia | 09.2012 - 07.2016

Advertising, marketing and technology tools for creation of advertisement products

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- GeekBrains «HTML&CSS» https://gb.ru/certificates/701170.en
- GeekBrains «ReactJS» https://gb.ru/certificates/863760.en